Guide to the Tri-State Conference on Manufacturing Records, 1978-1993 AIS.1993.10
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Employee Stock Ownership Plan Association Grassroots Lobbying Notebook for Pennsylvania ESOP Chapter (Box 39, Folder 60)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel Board, 1990 (Box 39, Folder 61)
- Star Wars: Defense or Death Star by Robert M. Bowman, 1985 (Box 39, Item 1)
- Labor Research Review, Fighting Rust: Labor-Community Struggles in Smokestack America, 1983 (Box 39, Item 2)
- Indicators of Economic Capacity (Box 40, Folder 1)
- Pollock Associates (Box 40, Folder 2)
- Road to Renaissance: Growth Industries for Pennsylvania (Box 40, Folder 3)
- National Financing (Box 40, Folder 4-13)
- Newspaper Clippings regarding Banking (Box 40, Folder 14)
- Financing: Alternative Investment Conference, 1989 (Box 40, Folder 15)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Financing: Community Reinvestment Act (Box 40, Folder 16)
- Military Remapping (Box 40, Folder 17)
- Mesta (Box 40, Folder 18)
- South Works/Chicago Steelworker Study (Box 40, Folder 19)
- Minimum Wage Campaign, National Unemployed Network (Box 40, Folder 20)
- Ad Hoc Committee to Counter KKK (Box 40, Folder 21)
- Campaign to End the Welfare Lein (Box 40, Folder 22)
- Tri-State Projects (Box 40, Folder 23)
- Choices for Pennsylvanians Status Report, June 1985 (Box 40, Item 1)
- Forging Revival and Renaissance: An Action Program for Revitalization of the Mon Valley and Technical Supplement by James O. Pickard, 1986 (Box 40, Item 2-3)
- A Strategy for Growth: An Economic Development Program for the Pittsburgh Region, Volume I and II (Box 40, Item 4-5)
- Steel Industry In Brief: Databook, USA, 1979-1980 (Box 40, Item 6)
- Technoeconomic Assessment of Electric Steelmaking Through the Year 2000, 1987 (Box 40, Item 7)
- Where Have All the Jobs Gone?: Causes of Job Loss, Past and Future in the Northwest Indiana Steel Industry (Box 40, Item 8)
- Pittsburgh Area Unemployment: The Community Response by Tom Foerster and David L. Donahoe, 1985 (Box 40, Item 9)
- Pass the Buck... Back!: The Community Reinvestment Handbook, 1979 (Box 40, Item 10)
- States and Communities: The Challenge for Economic Action by Nancy Barbe and June Sekera, 1983 (Box 40, Item 11)
- Pennsylvania Manufacturers Register, 1992 (Box 40, Item 12)
- Regional Industrial Buying Guide, 1992 (Box 40, Item 13)
- Caribbean Business to Business Guide, 1991 (Box 40, Item 14-15)
- Urban Redevelopment -- An Industrial Application by David William Elliot, 1953 (Box 41, Item 1)
- New Jersey Commission on Science & Technology, Annual Report, 1989 (Box 41, Item 2)
- Zeta Magazine (Box 41, Item 3)
- H.R. Krueger Machine Tool, Inc. and Michigan's "Get Smart" Gamble, 1987 (Box 41, Item 4)
- Citiparks: City of Pittsburgh Parks and Recreation, 1989 (Box 41, Item 5)
- Dialogue: A Debate and Discussion Journal by Federation for Industrial Retention and Renewal, October 1988 (Box 41, Item 6)
- Responding to Plant Closings in Tennessee: A Conference Sponsored by the Tennessee Industrial Renewal Network, June 2-3, 1989 (Box 41, Item 7)
- Economic Competitiveness: The States Take the Lead by David Osborne, 1987 (Box 41, Item 8)
- The Trade Picture: Year End 1990 by the AFL-CIO Economic Research Department, April 1991 (Box 41, Item 9)
- Community-Based Development: Investing in Renewal, September 1987 (Box 41, Item 10)
- Partial Shutdown of Diamond Tool & Horseshoe Company: Analysis, Outlook and Options for Public Intervention by Midwest Center for Labor Research, June 1987 (Box 41, Item 11)
- The Journal, Milwaukee, October 13, 1991 (Box 41, Item 12)
- Project Equality Update, 1991 (Box 41, Item 13)
- Positive Alternatives, 1991 (Box 41, Item 14)
- The South Pittsburgh Reporter, November 29, 1988, May 23 and June 13, 1989 (Box 41, Item 15-17)
- The Overlook, June-July 1988 and June-September 1989 (Box 41, Item 18-20)
- The New People by the Thomas Merton Center, August-September 1988 (Box 41, Item 21)
- The Greenfield Grapevine, August 1989 (Box 41, Item 22)
- Comprehension: The Ohio Bureau of Workers' Compensation Newsletter for Employees, 1989 (Box 41, Item 23)
- Jubilee: Social Concerns and the Episcopal Church, 1989 (Box 41, Item 24)
- Labor Notes, July 1989 (Box 41, Item 25)
- Plowshare, 1989 (Box 41, Item 26-27)
- Frontline, July 18, 1988 (Box 41, Item 28)
- APSOlution, May 1989 (Box 41, Item 29)
- Centennial Reports, 1989 (Box 41, Item 30-31)
- Pittsburgh Business Times Book of Business Lists, 1991 (Box 41, Item 32)
- The Book of Lists, 1991 (Box 41, Item 33)
- Employee Stock Ownership Plans, 1987 (Box 41, Folder 1)
- Center for Economic Conversion, 1990 (Box 41, Folder 2)
- UIU Health and Welfare Fund, 1992 (Box 41, Folder 3)
- United Steelworkers of America, 1988-1989 (Box 41, Folder 4)
- Miscellaneous Papers (Box 41, Folder 5)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 41, Folder 6)
- Contact Lists (Box 41, Folder 7)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel (Box 41, Folder 8)
- Organizations (Box 41, Folder 9)
- Board and Administrator Newsletter (Box 41, Folder 10)
- Newsletters and Articles (Box 41, Folder 11)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 41, Folder 12-13)
- Southbank Industry Association Information (Box 42, Folder 1)
- Non-Profit: Rayl Proposed By-Law Changes (Box 42, Folder 2)
- Southbank Industry Association Board Meeting, May 23, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 3)
- Non-Profit: Incorporators Revised By-Laws (Box 42, Folder 4)
- Southbank Industry Association: By-Lawsm Final Revision, May 30, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 5)
- Southbank Industry Association Financing (Box 42, Folder 6)
- Cooperative Assistance Fund (Box 42, Folder 7)
- Southbank Industry Association Financing Contacts, Social Investment Forum (Box 42, Folder 8)
- Ford Foundation (Box 42, Folder 9)
- Possible Investors (Box 42, Folder 10)
- Duquesne Light Economic Development Fund, 1990 (Box 42, Folder 11)
- Southbank Industry Association, Private Placement (Box 42, Folder 12)
- Southbank Industry Association Proposals, Three Rivers Community Fund (Box 42, Folder 13)
- Southbank Industry Association Financing, Fund-Raising Consultant (Box 42, Folder 14)
- Consultants: Frick and Stevenson (Box 42, Folder 15)
- Southbank Industry Association Proposal, Duquesne Light Fund (Box 42, Folder 16)
- Non-Profit Legal, Articles of Incorporation (Box 42, Folder 17)
- Non-Profit Legal, 501(c)(3) (Box 42, Folder 18)
- Non-Profit Legal, IRS Form 941 (Box 42, Folder 19)
- Southbank Industry Association Legal, Unrelated Business Income Tax (Box 42, Folder 20)
- Southbank Industry Association Legal, Title Holding Corporation Information (Box 42, Folder 21)
- CCAC Center-North Community Services Division (Box 42, Folder 22)
- Southbank Industry Association Mission Statement, March 1989 (Box 42, Folder 23)
- Southbank Industry Association Membership (Box 42, Folder 24)
- Stationary (Box 42, Folder 25)
- South Side Organizations, Brashear Associates (Box 42, Folder 26)
- South Side Organizations, South Side Local Development Corporation (Box 42, Folder 27)
- South Side Organizations, South Side Chamber of Commerce (Box 42, Folder 28)
- South Side Organizations, SPERT (Box 42, Folder 29)
- Electric Furnace Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 42, Folder 30-31)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Allegheny Ludlum Tour (Box 42, Folder 32)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Patrick Media Billboards (Box 42, Folder 33)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Brochure Materials (Box 42, Folder 34)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Bus Trip to Harrisburg, June 27, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 35)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, South Side Canvass (Box 42, Folder 36)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Churches (Box 42, Folder 37)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Labor Day, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 38)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign Logo (Box 42, Folder 39)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Outreach/Education Committee (Box 42, Folder 40)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Petitions (Box 42, Folder 41)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Posters (Box 42, Folder 42)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign, Speaking Engagements (Box 42, Folder 43)
- South Side Steel of Pittsburgh, Inc. Meeting, April 12, 1989 (Box 42, Folder 44)
- Electric Furnace Outreach Campaign Video (Box 42, Folder 45)
- Electric Furnace Committee, October 1987 (Box 42, Folder 46)
- LTV Downsizing Newspaper Clippings (Box 42, Folder 47)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: City Council Hearing, October 30, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 48)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: South Side Community Council Meeting, November 24, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 49)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Cleveland Rally, December 3, 1986 (Box 42, Folder 50)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Youngstown Rally, January 31, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 51)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Congressional Hearing, February 20, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 52)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Steel Valley Authority Tour, March 16, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 53)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: SOAR Washington, D.C. Trip, April 1, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 54)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Interim Meetings, May-June 1987 (Box 42, Folder 55)
- LTV Community/Worker Meeting, June 15, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 56)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV Mailing, July 24 (Box 42, Folder 57)
- South Side Outreach, Membership Meeting, December 14, 1987 (Box 42, Folder 58)
- Steel: LTV South Side, Technical Assistance Working Group (Box 42, Folder 59)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, Steel: Metals Retention Study (Box 42, Folder 60)
- Regional Reindustrialization Program, LTV: Position Paper (Box 42, Folder 61)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, LTV South Side (Box 42, Folder 62)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, LTV: Hazelwood Works Metals Survey (Box 42, Folder 63)
- Health Benefit Guaranty Corporation (Box 42, Folder 64)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Steel/Pension: Amsteel (Box 42, Folder 65)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, LTV: Contacts (Box 42, Folder 66)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, LTV: Solidarity (Box 42, Folder 67)
- South Side Furnace Buyout Committee (Box 42, Folder 68)
- GASP, Coke Batteries (Box 42, Folder 69)
- GASP, East End Alliance for Clean Air (Box 42, Folder 70)
- GASP Press Conference, November 10, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 71)
- South Side Local Development Company LTV Site Study (Box 42, Folder 72)
- Basic Steel Industry Conference, United Steelworkers of America Policy Statement, December 1988 (Box 42, Folder 73)
- MAGLEV (Box 43)
- Democrat Presidential Candidate Debate, 1988 (Box 44, Folder 1)
- Duquesne Feasibility Study Attachements (Box 44, Folder 2)
- Duquesne Attachments (Box 44, Folder 3)
- Ohio Valley Industrial Retention and Renewal, 1986-1990 (Box 44, Folder 4)
- Leece-Neville Plant in Cleveland (Box 44, Folder 5)
- Upper Ohio Valley Reindustrialization Project (Box 44, Folder 6)
- The Case for Manufacturing in Western Pennsylvania (Box 44, Folder 7)
- Letter to Buyers of the Tri-State Coloring Book, 1993 (Box 44, Folder 8)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project, Natural Resources (Box 44, Folder 9)
- River Ran Red Movie Poster (Box 44, Folder 10)
- Labor Notes "New Directions for Labor" Conference Mailing List, 1989 (Box 44, Folder 11)
- Home Ownership Protective Effort Brochures by Housing Opportunities, Inc. (Box 44, Folder 12)
- Historical Society of Western Pennsylvania (Box 44, Folder 13)
- Crossroads for America: Choosing a Better Future for American Industry and the American People (Box 44, Folder 14)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Industrial Resource Centers (Box 44, Folder 15-16)
- Rebuilding During the 1980's: Report of the Comptroller, May 7, 1979 (Box 44, Item 1)
- Neighborhoods: A Self-Help Sampler (Box 44, Item 2)
- Pennsylvania Council of the Arts: Guide to Programs and Services, 1986 (Box 44, Item 3)
- Graphic Art Materials Reference Manual (Box 44, Item 4)
- Cartooning the Head & Figure by Jack Hamm, 1978 (Box 44, Item 5)
- Clem Williams Films 16mm Rental Movies, 1981 (Box 44, Item 6)
- Journal of Planning Education and Research, 1988 (Box 44, Item 7)
- What 100 New Jobs Mean to a Community, 1985 (Box 44, Item 8)
- America's Steel Industry: A Time to Act (Box 44, Item 9)
- Steelabor Article "Employee Stock Ownership Plan: USWA Workers Become Owners", July 1988 (Box 44, Item 10)
- Oakland, December 1988 (Box 44, Item 11)
- Specific Cluster Proposal for Three Site Considerations by the Steel Industry Heritage Task Force, June 8, 1988 (Box 44, Item 12)
- Starting with Real Worker-Management Cooperation: The Lessons of Steel in the Mon Valley by John Hoerr, May 20, 1988 (Box 44, Item 13)
- For a National Industrial Policy That Will Create Jobs by Dr. Ann Markusen, May 20, 1988 (Box 44, Item 14)
- Steel Industry Heritage Task Force Committee Minutes, May 24, 1988 (Box 44, Item 15)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel: Ten Years of a Labor/Community Alliance (Box 44, Item 16)
- Plant Closings: A National Response (Box 44, Item 17)
- Steelabor, February 1985, November-December 1988, February-March 1989 (Box 44, Item 18-20)
- Homestead as History: Securing Historical Sites in Anticipation of the 1992 Centennial, May 10, 1988 (Box 44, Item 21)
- The Data Center Search Service (Box 44, Item 22)
- Cleveland Coalition Against Plant Closings Newsletter, January 1989 (Box 44, Item 23)
- Labor Outreach (Box 44, Item 24)
- Citizens' Newsletter for Low-Level Radioactive Waste Disposal, 1989 (Box 44, Item 25)
- Across the Table, 1989 (Box 44, Item 26)
- Midwest Center for Labor Research Annual Report, 1987-1988 (Box 44, Item 27)
- Speedlines by the High Speed Rail Association, August-September 1988, November 1989 (Box 44, Item 28-29)
- Coalition of Northeastern Governors Connection, October 1988, May 1989 (Box 44, Item 30-31)
- The New People by the Thomas Merton Center, July 1988 (Box 44, Item 32)
- PHLF News, 1988 (Box 44, Item 33)
- The Working People's News, July and December 1988 (Box 44, Item 34)
- Board and Administrator (Box 44, Item 35)
- The Affirmative Action Plan for the NEA, 1989 (Box 44, Item 36)
- Frank Lucchino for Mayor Packet (Box 44, Item 37)
- The Pittsburgh Press Sunday Magazine, December 4, 1988 (Box 44, Item 38)
- Center for Economic Conversion Annual Report, 1989 (Box 44, Item 39)
- Pennsylvania Labor History Society Mother Jones Award Announcement (Box 44, Item 40)
- Focus by Carnegie Mellon University, November-December 1989 (Box 44, Item 41)
- Inc.: The Magazine for Growing Companies, December 1989 (Box 44, Item 42)
- Corporate America's Biggest Export: Our Jobs (Box 44, Item 43)
- Betraying the Trust: The Pittston Company's Drive to Break Appalachia's Coalfield Communities (Box 44, Item 44)
- Generations: The Newsletter of Southeast Women's Employment Coalition, 1989 (Box 44, Item 45)
- Pittsburgh by University of Pittsburgh Press, New Fall Books, 1989 (Box 44, Item 46)
- Ten Tested Ways to Take More Cash Out of Your Small Business (Box 44, Item 47)
- Positive Alternative, 1989 (Box 44, Item 48)
- CMP Newsletter, August 1989 (Box 44, Item 49)
- On the Market, March-April 1988 (Box 44, Item 50)
- The Greenfield Grapevine, November-December 1988 (Box 44, Item 51-52)
- Labor Notes, April, August-September 1989 (Box 44, Item 53-55)
- Ploughshare, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Item 56-58)
- Plowshare, 1989 (Box 44, Item 59)
- The Overlook, December 1988, January, October-December 1989, January 1990 (Box 44, Item 60-62)
- The South Pittsburgh Reporter, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Item 63-68)
- Jobs Impact Bulletin, 1988-1989 (Box 44, Item 69-73)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 45, Folder 1-3)
- Clippings: Bankruptcies/Companies (Box 45, Folder 4)
- Clippings: Brake & Switch (Box 45, Folder 5)
- Clippings: Disinvestment/Unemployment, National (Box 45, Folder 6)
- Clippings: Disinvestment/Unemployment, Region (Box 45, Folder 7)
- Clippings: Dorothy 6 (Box 45, Folder 8)
- Clippings: Economic Summit (Box 45, Folder 9)
- Clippings: Federation for Industrial retention and Renewal (Box 45, Folder 10)
- Clippings: Homestead Works (Box 45, Folder 11)
- Clippings: Industrial Capital Fund (Box 45, Folder 12)
- Clippings: LTV (Box 45, Folder 13)
- Clippings: LTV, South Side Electric Furnaces (Box 45, Folder 14)
- Clippings: Metals Retention Study (Box 45, Folder 15)
- Clippings: Mon Valley Expressway (Box 45, Folder 16)
- Clippings: Pensions (Box 45, Folder 17)
- Clippings (Box 45, Folder 18)
- Clippings: Reindustrialization (Box 45, Folder 19)
- Clippings: Regional Reindustrialization Program, Cleveland (Box 45, Folder 20)
- Clippings: Reindustrialization/RUDAT Plans (Box 45, Folder 21)
- Clippings: Regional Reindustrialization Program, Wheeling (Box 45, Folder 22)
- Clippings: Steel Industry (Box 45, Folder 23)
- Clippings: Steel Valley Authority (Box 45, Folder 24)
- Clippings: Tri-State (Box 45, Folder 25-28)
- Attachments: Appendicies, 1989 (Box 45, Folder 29)
- Attachments: Budgets, 1985-1990 (Box 45, Folder 30-35)
- Attachments: Letters of Support (Box 45, Folder 36)
- Attachments: News Clippings (Box 45, Folder 37)
- Attachments: Resumes (Box 45, Folder 38)
- Funding (Box 45, Folder 39)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1987 (Box 45, Folder 40)
- Government Fundraising: Community Development Block Grants (Box 45, Folder 41)
- Government Fundraising: Department of Community Affairs (Box 45, Folder 42)
- Government Fundraising: Vista (Box 45, Folder 43)
- Amsteel (Box 45, Folder 44)
- Bankruptcies/Companies (Box 45, Folder 45)
- Budgets Sent with Proposals (Box 45, Folder 46)
- Economic Development Funding (Box 45, Folder 47)
- Eastern Industrial Valleys Community of Faith (Box 45, Folder 48)
- Eminent Domain (Box 45, Folder 49)
- Newsletters and Articles (Box 46, Folder 1)
- Handwritten Notes (Box 46, Folder 2)
- Correspondence (Box 46, Folder 3)
- Miscellaneous Papers and Pamphlets (Box 46, Folder 4)
- Tri-State and Related Organizations (Box 46, Folder 5)
- Other Organizations (Box 46, Folder 6)
- Annemarie Draham Tri-State Time Sheets (Box 46, Folder 7)
- Agenda, 1988-1989 (Box 46, Folder 8)
- Fundraising (Box 46, Folder 9-26)
- Membership (Box 46, Folder 27-34)
- Tri-State Conference on Steel Newsbulletin, March 1987 (Box 46, Folder 35)
- Newspaper Clippings (Box 46, Folder 36-37)
- Regional Reindustrialization Project Master Proposal (Box 46, Folder 38)
- Information for Brochures (Box 46, Folder 39)
- Labor Research Review Subscriber List, June 1986 (Box 46, Folder 40)
- Tri-State Membership Drive (Box 46, Folder 41)
- Direct Mail: Special Appeal, Legal Intern (Box 46, Folder 42)
- Direct Mail: Newsletter Solicitations (Box 46, Folder 43)
- What Can We Do About Plant Closings? by Tri-State Conference on the Impact of Steel (Box 46, Item 1)
- A Dialogue Between the Religious and Labor Community on Social and Ethical Concerns in a Changing Society, January 25-27, 1989 (Box 46, Item 2)
- Men of Steel: Collected Poems by Alice Gray Gaydos, 1980 (Box 46, Item 3)
- UIU Health and Welfare Fund: Summary Plan Description, January 1988 (Box 46, Item 4)
- General Assembly of Pennsylvania, House Bill No. 63 Creating the Pennsylvania Industrial Development Finance Corporation, 1989 (Box 46, Item 5)
- General Assembly of Pennsylvania, Senate Bill No. 269 Creating the Pennsylvania Industrial Development Finance Corporation, January 1989 (Box 46, Item 6)
- Reference Material regarding Finance/Mergers and Acquisitions (Box 47, Folder 1)
- Tri-State Financial Reports (Box 47, Folder 2)
- Government Intervention, Pennsylvania (Box 47, Folder 3)
- Government Intervention, Other States (Box 47, Folder 4)
- Government Intervention, Pittsburgh and Allegheny County (Box 47, Folder 5)
- Government Intervention, United States (Box 47, Folder 6)
- Interreligious Economic Crisis Organizing Network, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 7)
- Industrial Heartlands University (Box 47, Folder 8)
- Industrial Museums (Box 47, Folder 9)
- Industrial Policy/Anti-Takeover Laws (Box 47, Folder 10)
- Industrial Policy, Cuomo Commission (Box 47, Folder 11)
- Industrial Policy (Box 47, Folder 12)
- Industrial Policy, Plant Closing Legislation (Box 47, Folder 13)
- Industrial Policy, "Preparedness" (Box 47, Folder 14)
- Industrial Policy, Trade Policy (Box 47, Folder 15)
- Insurance for Staff (Box 47, Folder 16)
- Local Initiatives Support Corporation (Box 47, Folder 17)
- LTV (Box 47, Folder 18)
- Tri-State Mailing List Program (Box 47, Folder 19)
- Magnetic Levitation (MAGLEV) (Box 47, Folder 20)
- Manufacturing Facilities and Companies in Pennsylvania/Westinghouse (Box 47, Folder 21)
- Metropolitanism (Box 47, Folder 22)
- Pensions and Other Employee Benefits (Box 47, Folder 23)
- Tri-State Proposals, Cleveland (Box 47, Folder 24)
- Tri-State Proposals, Regional Reindustrialization Projects (Box 47, Folder 25)
- Proposals by Other Groups (Box 47, Folder 26)
- Tri-State Proposals, Pittsburgh (Box 47, Folder 27)
- Recycling and Cogeneration (Box 47, Folder 28)
- Reindustrialization Strategies (Box 47, Folder 29-30)
- Reindustrialization Schemes, Regional Urban Design Assistance Team Plans (Box 47, Folder 31)
- Reindustrialization Schemes, State Funding and Budgets (Box 47, Folder 32)
- Tax Base, Mon Valley (Box 47, Folder 33)
- Zoning (Box 47, Folder 34)
- Tri-State Board Retraining/Restructuring (Box 47, Folder 35)
- Tri-State Staff Training Resources (Box 47, Folder 36)
- Tri-State Staff Training Workshop, March 1, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 37)
- Discover Total Resources: A Guide for Nonprofits by Mellon Bank (Box 47, Folder 38)
- Campaign for Human Development, 1981-1985 (Box 47, Folder 39-42)
- Employee Records, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 43)
- Staff Finances, 1987-1988 (Box 47, Folder 44)
- Campaign for Human Development Quarterly Reports, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 45-47)
- Tri-State Grant Contracts, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 48)
- Commission on Religion in Appalachia, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 49)
- Episcopal Diocese of Pittsburgh, 1988-1989 (Box 47, Folder 50)
- Needmor, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 51)
- Sterns Report, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 52)
- Check Request Forms and Receipts (Box 47, Folder 53)
- Bank Statements, 1986-1988 (Box 47, Folder 54-56)
- Tri-State Bills, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 57)
- Tri-State Finances (Box 48)
- Financial Documents (Box 49, Folder 1)
- Western Pennsylvania Advanced Technology Center Overall Program Summary, 1987-1988 (Box 49, Folder 2)
- Enterprise Corporation of Pittsburgh, 1989 (Box 49, Folder 3)
- Pamphlets (Box 49, Folder 4)
- Employee Stock Ownership Programs (Box 49, Folder 5)
- Organizations (Box 49, Folder 6)
- Fundraising and Finances (Box 49, Folder 7)
- Articles and Newspaper Clippings (Box 49, Folder 8)
- Federation on Industrial Retention and Renewal (Box 49, Folder 9)
- DSL: Specialists in Pooled Financing Programs (Box 49, Folder 10)
- Christian Brothers Investment Services (Box 49, Folder 11)
- Our Canada or Theirs? by the Canadian Labour Congress (Box 49, Folder 12)
- Intelligent Technology (Box 49, Folder 13)
- Southwestern Pennsylvania Industrial Resource Center (Box 49, Folder 14)
- Pittsburgh History and Landmarks Foundation (Box 49, Folder 15)
- Photographs (Box 49, Item 1)
- America's Industrial Heritage Project Action Plan, 1987 (Box 49, Item 2)
- In Pittsburgh, February 3-9, 1988 (Box 49, Item 3)
- Three Rivers Industrial District (Box 49, Item 4)
- Labor History Calendar by the Pacific Northwest Labor History Association, 1990 (Box 49, Item 5)
- Pittsburgh High Technology (Box 49, Item 6)
- Executive Report: Pittsburgh's Business Magazine, November 1989 (Box 49, Item 7)
- Washington's Landing (Box 49, Item 8)
- Planning Your Business: Guide for Smaller Businesses and Entrepreneurs by Price Waterhouse (Box 49, Item 9)
- Final Report, Survey of Small and Medium-Sized Manufacturing Companies in Southwestern Pennsylvania: Results and Recommendations by Dr. Roger S. Ahlbrandt, Jr., July 1987 (Box 49, Item 10-11)
- University Times Annual Research Supplement (Box 49, Item 12)